Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection MSS.040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize: Series II: Graphic Material, 40670
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork, 40931
    - Williams, Richard-Films-RAGGEDYANN & ANDY, undated; 40932 (Box II.A.8, Folder 44)
  - Subseries B: Posters, 40671
    NOTE: () denotes the number of posters
    - Abbeville Celebrates the Real McCay (2), undated; 40688 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Animated World of John Canemaker (3), 1979; 40687 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Cambridge (UK) Animation Film Festival, 1981; 40686 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Fischinger: A Retrospective of His Paintings & Films, Gallery 609, Denver, 1980; 40685 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Independent Cinema, Film Forum, Winter 1977, New York, 40684 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art Film Bulletin, Oct. & Nov. [1977?], 40683 (Folder 5 Right)
    - NewAmerican Filmmakers Series, Whitney Museum of Art, New York, Fall 1975 and Winter 1975/1976, 40682 (Folder 5 Right)
    - 19th International Tournee of Animation, 1986; 40680 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Oskar Fischinger: "The WorkingProcess", Theatre Vanguard, Los Angeles, 1976; 40679 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Oskar Fischinger Programma, Melkweg Cinema, Amsterdam (Holland), undated; 40678 (Folder 8)
    - The Walter Lantz Conference onAnimation, Los Angeles, 1987; 40677 (Folder 8)
    - The2nd Annual Walter Lantz Conference on Animation, Los Angeles, 1988; 40676 (Folder 8)
    - The Television Laboratory at Thirteen, 1972-1984; 40675 (Folder 8)
    - UBU, an Animated Film by GeoffDunbar, undated; 40674 (Folder 8)
    - WarnerBros. Cartoons Golden Jubilee, Museum of Modern Art, New York, 1985-1986; 40673 (Folder 8)
    - THE WIZARD'S SON, 1981 (8), 40672 (Folder 5 Right)
- Accretions 2000 - Series I: Documentary Material, 40529
  Documentary material includes interview transcripts, research notes, correspondence, film production drafts and outlines, news articles and promotional materials.
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 40665
    - Disney Institute press kit, 1995; 40669 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 1)
    - Dreamworks Studios: PRINCE OF EGYPT, undated; 40668 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 2)
    - 22nd Annual Annie Awards, 1994; 40667 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 3)
    - Warner Brothers Studios: IRON GIANT, undated; 40666 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: People, 40530
    - Algar, James, undated; 40664 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 5)
    - Allers, Roger, undated; 40663 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, Ken, undated; 40662 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 7-9)
    - Baer, Jane, undated; 40661 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 10)
    - Barks, Carl, undated; 40660 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 11)
    - Barrier, Michael, undated; 40659 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 13)
    - Baytos, Betsy, undated; 40658 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 14)
    - Bell, Carl, undated; 40657 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 15)
    - Bertino, Al, undated; 40656 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 16)
    - Bluth, Don, undated; 40655 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 17)
    - Bodrero, Jim, undated; 40654 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 18)
    - Bosson, Jack: Notes from Story Development Workshop, 1997; 40653 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 19)
    - Brightman, Homer, undated; 40652 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 20)
    - Brizzi, Paul, undated; 40651 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 21)
    - Canemaker, John: Paper Dreams, undated; 40650 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 22-24)
    - Champion, Marge, undated; 40649 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 25)
    - Chapman, Brenda, undated; 40648 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 26)
    - Clemmons, Larry, undated; 40647 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 27)
    - Coates, Claude, undated; 40646 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 28)
    - Codrick, Tom, undated; 40645 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 29)
    - Colvig, Pinto, undated; 40644 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 30-31)
    - Cottrell, Bill, undated; 40643 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 32-33)
    - Crump, Roland, undated; 40642 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 34)
    - Culhane, John, undated; 40641 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 35)
    - DaGradi, Don, undated; 40640 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 36)
    - DeBlois, Dean, undated; 40639 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 37)
    - Deja, Andreas, undated; 40638 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 38)
    - Disney, Roy O., undated; 40637 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 39)
    - Disney, Walt: Employee Evaluations, 1938-1940; 40636 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 40)
    - Disney, Walt: Memos - miscellaneous, undated; 40635 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 41)
    - Disney, Walt: Personnel Data - miscellaneous, undated; 40634 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 42)
    - Disney, Walt: Studio strike, 1941; 40633 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 43)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - ALICE IN WONDERLAND, 1951; 40632 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 44)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - Animation Drafts (various), undated; 40631 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 44)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - BAMBI, undated; 40630 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 46)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - BAND CONCERT, 1934; 40629 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 47)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE BRAVE LITTLE TAILOR, 1937-1938; 40628 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 48)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - COUNTRY COUSIN, undated; 40627 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 49)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - GODDESS OF SPRING, 1934; 40626 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 50)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - HOW TO... (various titles featuring Goofy), undated; 40625 (Box 2000.I.A.B.1, Folder 51)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - JUNGLE BOOK, 1967; 40624 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 52)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - KINGDOM OF THE SUN, 1997; 40623 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 53)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - LADY AND THE TRAMP, undated; 40622 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 54)
    - Disney, Walt: Lecia reel memo, undated; 40621 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 55)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE LITTLE WHIRLWIND, undated; 40620 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 56)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - MAKE MINE MUSIC, 1945; 40619 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 57)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE OLD MILL, 1936; 40618 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 58)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - 101 DALMATIONS, undated; 40617 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 59)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - PETER PAN, 1952; 40616 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 60)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - PINOCCHIO, undated; 40615 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 61)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE RESCUERS, 1977; 40614 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 62)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - SNOW WHITE AND THE SEVEN DWARFS, undated; 40613 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 64)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - SORCERER'S APPRENTICE, undated; 40612 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 65)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - SWORD IN THE STONE, 1962-1963; 40611 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 66)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THREE CABALLEROS, 1944; 40610 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 67)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - WYNKEN, BLYNKEN AND NOD, 1936-1938; 40609 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 68)
    - Disney-Miller, Diane, undated; 40608 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 69)
    - Engel, Jules, undated; 40607 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 70)
    - Ewing, John, undated; 40606 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 71)
    - Fallberg, Carl, undated; 40605 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 72)
    - Ferguson, Norm, undated; 40604 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 73)
    - Fischinger, Oscar, undated; 40603 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 74)
    - Fujikawa, Gyo, undated; 40602 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 75)
    - Gerry, Vance, undated; 40601 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 76)
    - Gillett, Burt, undated; 40600 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 77)
    - Gombert, Ed, undated; 40599 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 78)
    - Grant, Campbell, undated; 40598 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 79)
    - Hansen, Ed, undated; 40597 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 80)
    - Harkey, Kevin, undated; 40596 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 81)
    - Haskett, Dan, undated; 40595 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 82)
    - Hee, T. (Thorton), undated; 40594 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 83-84)
    - Horvath, Ferdinand, undated; 40593 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 85)
    - Huemer, Dick, undated; 40592 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 86-88)
    - Hurd, Earl, undated; 40591 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 89)
    - Husband, Ron, undated; 40590 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 90)
    - Ising, Rudy, undated; 40589 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 91)
    - Iwerks, Ub, undated; 40588 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 92)
    - Jackson, Wilfred, undated; 40587 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 93)
    - Johnson, Barry, undated; 40586 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 94)
    - Jones, Volus, undated; 40585 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 95)
    - Keane, Glen, undated; 40584 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 96)
    - Kelsey, Dick, undated; 40583 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 97)
    - Kinney, Jack, undated; 40582 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 98)
    - Kley, Heinrich, undated; 40581 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 99)
    - Legg, J. Gordon, undated; 40580 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 100)
    - Luske, Ham, undated; 40579 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 101)
    - Lyons, Michael, undated; 40578 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 102)
    - Mattinson, Burny, undated; 40577 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 103)
    - Michener, Dave, undated; 40576 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 104)
    - Miller, Jack, undated; 40575 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 105)
    - Natwick, Grim, undated; 40574 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 106)
    - Noble, Maurice, undated; 40573 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 107)
    - O'Connor, Ken, undated; 40572 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 108)
    - Oliver, Dale, undated; 40571 (Box 2000.I.B.2, Folder 109)
    - Peet, Bill, undated; 40570 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 110)
    - Penner, Erdman, undated; 40569 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 111)
    - Peterson, Ken, undated; 40568 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 112)
    - Petty, Sara, undated; 40567 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 113)
    - Plummer, Elmer, undated; 40566 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 114)
    - Pomeroy, John, undated; 40565 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 115)
    - Provensen, Martin, undated; 40564 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 116)
    - Putnam, Thor, undated; 40563 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 117)
    - Ranft, Joe, undated; 40562 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 118)
    - Reeves, Harry, undated; 40561 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 119)
    - Richmond, Neil, undated; 40560 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 120)
    - Rinaldi, Joe, undated; 40559 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 121)
    - Ring, Borge, undated; 40558 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 122)
    - Salkin, Leo, undated; 40557 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 123)
    - Sanders, Chris, undated; 40556 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 124)
    - Schumacher, Thomas, undated; 40555 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 125)
    - Scott, Retta, undated; 40554 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 126)
    - Sears, Ted, undated; 40553 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 127)
    - Sharpsteen, Ben, undated; 40552 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 128)
    - Shaw, Mel, undated; 40551 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 129)
    - Sito, Tom, undated; 40550 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 130)
    - Smith, David, undated; 40549 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 131)
    - Smith, Paul, undated; 40548 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 132)
    - Smith, Webb, undated; 40547 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 133)
    - Southworth, Ken, undated; 40546 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 134)
    - Stallings, George, undated; 40545 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 135)
    - Sterner, Robert, undated; 40544 (Box 2000.I.B.3, Folder 136)
    - Takamoto, Iwao, undated; 40543 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 137)
    - Thomas, Bob: Art of Animation, 1954; 40542 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 138-139)
    - Trousdale, Gary, undated; 40541 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 140)
    - Weeks, Clair, undated; 40540 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 141)
    - West, Tiger, undated; 40539 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 142)
    - Wightman, Kelly, undated; 40538 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 143)
    - Williams, Chris, undated; 40537 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 144)
    - Williams, Richard, undated; 40536 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 145)
    - Williams, Roy, undated; 40535 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 146)
    - Wise, Kirk, undated; 40534 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 147)
    - Wong, Tyrus, undated; 40533 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 148)
    - Young, Cy, undated; 40532 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 149)
    - Young, Pete, undated; 40531 (Box 2000.I.B.4, Folder 150)
- Accretions 2000 - Oversize - Series I: Documentary Material, 40526
  - Subseries B: People, 40527
    - Barks, Carl, undated; 40528 (Box 2000.I.B.5, Folder 12)
- Accretions 2001 - Series I: Documentary Material, 40514
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 40523
    - Disney Action Analysis Studies, undated; 40525 (Box 2001.I.A.1, Folder 1-4)
    - United Productions of America, undated; 40524 (Box 2001.I.A.B.2, Folder 5-7)
  - Subseries B: People, 40515
    - Babbitt, Art, undated; 40522 (Box 2001.I.A.B.2, Folder 9-10)
    - Babbitt, Art, undated; 40521 (Box 2001.I.B.3, Folder 11)
    - Hubley, John and Faith, undated; 40520 (Box 2001.I.B.3, Folder 12-14)
    - Hubley, John and Faith, undated; 40519 (Box 2001.I.B.4, Folder 15-16)
    - Messmer, Otto, undated; 40518 (Box 2001.I.B.4, Folder 17-18)
    - Messmer, Otto, undated; 40517 (Box 2001.I.B.5, Folder 19-22)
    - Tissa, David, undated; 40516 (Box 2001.I.B.5, Folder 23)
- Accretions 2001 - Oversize - Series I: Documentary Material, 40511
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 40512
    - United Productions of America: Mr. Boing Boing, undated; 40513 (Box 2001.I.A.6, Folder 8)
- Accretions 2001 - Oversize - Series II: GraphicMaterial, 40505
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork, 40506
    - Hubley, John and Faith, undated; 40510 (Box 2001.II.A.6, Folder 24)
    - Messmer, Otto: Felix the Cat, undated; 40509 (Box 2001.II.A.6, Folder 25)
    - Tissa, David (original pencil sketches), undated; 40508 (Box 2001.II.A.6, Folder 26)
    - Unknown artist, undated; 40507 (Box 2001.II.A.6, Folder 27)
- Accretions 2003 - Series I: Documentary Material, 40422
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 40494
    - Animal Sketching (photocopy), undated; 40504 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 1)
    - Animation Storyboarding, undated; 40503 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 2)
    - Cooper Union Portfolio Folder, undated; 40502 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 3)
    - Disney: Assorted Animation Brochures, undated; 40501 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 4)
    - Disney: Assorted Production Documents, undated; 40500 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 5)
    - Disney: Assorted Production Meeting Transcripts, undated; 40499 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 6)
    - General Animation Research (news clippings), 1999-2001; 40498 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 7)
    - General Animation Research (notes), 1999-2001; 40497 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 8)
    - General Art Research, undated; 40496 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 9)
    - The Mousetrap (photocopy of off-the-record drawings by Disney artists), 1937; 40495 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: People, 40423
    - Canemaker, John: AIDS Dance-a-thon, 1991; 40493 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 11)
    - Canemaker, John: Angels on Ice, 1994; 40492 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 12)
    - Canemaker, John: Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, undated; 40491 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 13)
    - Canemaker, John: The Art of the Hubleys, undated; 40490 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 14)
    - Canemaker, John: Authored Press (various articles), 1972-1996; 40489 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 15)
    - Canemaker, John: Awards, undated; 40488 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 16)
    - Canemaker, John: Before the Animation Begins, undated; 40487 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 17)
    - Canemaker, John: Biographical material, undated; 40486 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 18)
    - Canemaker, John: BOTTOM'S DREAM, undated; 40485 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 19-20)
    - Canemaker, John: BREAK THE SILENCE, undated; 40484 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 21)
    - Canemaker, John: BRIDGEHAMPTON, undated; 40483 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 22-23)
    - Canemaker, John: Chemical Abstracts (Kaz), undated; 40482 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 24)
    - Canemaker, John: CONFESSIONS OF A STAND-UP, undated; 40481 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 25-26)
    - Canemaker, John: CONFESSIONS OF A STAR DREAMER, undated; 40480 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 27)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Department of the Army, 1967; 40479 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 28)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Film Festival-related, 1973-1996; 40478 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 29)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1974-1997; 40477 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 30)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Ninomiya, Yoko, 1987-1989; 40476 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 31)
    - Canemaker, John: The Creative Spirit, undated; 40475 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 32-33)
    - Canemaker, John: Dennis Blair Folder, undated; 40474 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 34)
    - Canemaker, John: DUMBO (DVD commentary), undated; 40473 (Box 2003.I.A.B.1, Folder 35)
    - Canemaker, John: DUMBO (DVD commentary), undated; 40472 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 36)
    - Canemaker, John: DUMBO (story outline), 1976; 40471 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 37)
    - Canemaker, John: Felix: the Twisted Tale..., undated; 40470 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 38)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), 1977-1979; 40469 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 39)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), 1980-1989; 40468 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 40)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), 1990-1999; 40467 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 41)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), undated; 40466 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 42)
    - Canemaker, John: FOCUS Awards, undated; 40465 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 43)
    - Canemaker, John: Grant Supporting Material, undated; 40464 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 44)
    - Canemaker, John: Hiroshima '85 (film festival), 1985; 40463 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 45)
    - Canemaker, John: How to get Blessed Without Sneezing, undated; 40462 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 46)
    - Canemaker, John: JOHN LENNON SCKETCHBOOK, undated; 40461 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 47-48)
    - Canemaker, John: The MacDowell Colony Newsletter, 1997; 40460 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 49)
    - Canemaker, John: Marymount Manhattan College Alumni Recognition Award, 1997; 40459 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 50)
    - Canemaker, John: Marymount Manhattan College President's Report, 1997; 40458 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 51)
    - Canemaker, John: PAPER DREAMS, undated; 40457 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 52)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), 1959-1979; 40456 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 53)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), 1980-1989; 40455 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 54)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), 1990-1999; 40454 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 55)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), undated; 40453 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 56)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Releases, undated; 40452 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 57)
    - Canemaker, John: PS 1: Animations, undated; 40451 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 58)
    - Canemaker, John: Request, undated; 40450 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 59)
    - Canemaker, John: SNOW WHITE (DVD commentary), undated; 40449 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 60-61)
    - Canemaker, John: Tex Avery: The Great Animation Director, undated; 40448 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 62)
    - Canemaker, John: WHAT DO CHILDREN THINK..., undated; 40447 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 63)
    - Canemaker, John: Winsor McCay: His Life and Art, undated; 40446 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 64)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WIZARD'S SUN, undated; 40445 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 65)
    - Canemaker, John: Woman of the Year, undated; 40444 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 66)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WORLD ACCORDING TO GARP, undated; 40443 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 67)
    - Canemaker, John: YOU DON'T HAVE TO DIE, undated; 40442 (Box 2003.I.B.2, Folder 68-70)
    - Charlot, Jean, undated; 40441 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 71)
    - Disney, Walt (biographical material - Missouri), undated; 40440 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 72)
    - Ewing, John, undated; 40439 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 73)
    - Graham, Don, undated; 40438 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 74)
    - Graham, Don: The Art of Animation, 1955; 40437 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 75-76)
    - Grant, Joe, undated; 40436 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 77)
    - Keane, Glen, undated; 40435 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 78)
    - Kentridge, William, undated; 40434 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 79)
    - Lasseter, John, undated; 40433 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 80)
    - Mitchell, Mark, undated; 40432 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 81)
    - Moore, Fred, undated; 40431 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 82)
    - Peterson, Ken, undated; 40430 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 83)
    - Williams, Richard, undated; 40429 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 84)
    - Williams, Richard: Master Class Lectures, 1997; 40428 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 85-86)
    - Williams, Richard: photographs, undated; 40427 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 87)
    - Williams, Richard: promotional materials, 1974; 40426 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 88)
    - Williams, Richard: Raggedy Ann and Andy (original script with annotations), undated; 40425 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 89)
    - Williams, Richard: Raggedy Ann and Andy (slides and photographs), undated; 40424 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 90)
- Accretions 2003 - Series II: Graphic Material, 40380
  Conditions Governing Access
  One file in Series II Subseries A has been restricted by the collection donor. This file will become avaiable to researchers in March 2023.
  Unless otherwise noted, graphic materials are copies of originals.
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork, 40381
    - Blair, Mary: ALICE IN WONDERLAND, undated; 40421 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 92)
    - Blair, Mary: from Animated Research Lab (ARL), undated; 40420 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 93)
    - Blair, Mary: assorted, undated; 40419 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 95)
    - Blair, Mary: CINDERELLA, undated; 40418 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 99)
    - Blair, Mary: commercial artwork, undated; 40417 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 100)
    - Blair, Mary: It's a Small World, undated; 40416 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 103)
    - Blair, Mary: from Kevin Blair Collection, undated; 40415 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 104)
    - Blair, Mary: PETER PAN, undated; 40414 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 105)
    - Blair, Mary: Personal art and greeting cards, undated; 40413 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 106)
    - Blair, Mary: from Walt Disney Art Library, undated; 40412 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 107)
    - Clark, Les, undated; 40411 (Box 2003.I.B.II.A.3, Folder 108)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Gabriel, Mike, undated; 40410 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 114)
    - Grant, Joe, undated; 40409 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 115)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated; 40408 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 118-119)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated; 40407 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 123-124)
    - Lounsberry, John, undated; 40406 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 128)
    - Moore, Fred, undated; 40405 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 131)
    - Tytla, Adrienne, undated; 40404 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 135)
    - Tytla, William: BRAVE LITTLE TAILOR, undated; 40403 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 136)
    - Tytla, William: COCK O' THE WALK, 1935; 40402 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 137)
    - Tytla, William: REASON AND EMOTION (Hitler sketchs), undated; 40401 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 138)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - Devil sequence #11-69, undated; 40400 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 139)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - Devil sequence #11-75, undated; 40399 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 140)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - Devil sketches, undated; 40398 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 141)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - various sketches, undated; 40397 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 142)
    - Tytla, William: PINOCCHIO: Stromboli, undated; 40396 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 144)
    - Tytla, William: SNOW WHITE: Dwarfs, 1937; 40395 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 146-147)
    - Tytla, William: Self-portraits and caricatures, undated; 40394 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 148)
    - Tytla, William: THE SULTAN'S CAT, 1931; 40393 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 149)
    - Tytla, William: Various sketches, undated; 40392 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 150-151)
    - Tytla, William: Photos, undated; 40391 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 152)